Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Public Relations records, 1934-1999 and undated RL.11700
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accounts and New Business, 1949-1997 and undated; 2
  - National Shoe Institute--Holiday promotion, 1949; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - National Shoe Institute--National shoe fairs, 1949; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - National Shoe Institute--Spring campaign, 1949 (Box 12)
  - National Shoe Institute--Spring promotion, 1950; 11 folders (Box 12)
  - National Shoe Institute--Spring promotion (includes "Beams" newsletter), 1950 (Box 35)
  - National Shoe Institute--Spring promotion, 1950 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Nestle, 1984-1995; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Nestle--Nestea, 1982 (Box 13)
  - New business prime target list, 1983 (Box 13)
  - New York Arrows (sports team), 1981 (Box 13)
  - New York Cares coat drive, 1991-1994 (Box 13)
  - New York City Opera, 1982 (Box 13)
  - New York Jazz Museum, 1975 (Box 13)
  - New York Port Authority--Staggered Work Hours Plan, 1974 (Box 13)
  - NordicTrack, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Norfolk Southern, 1991-1993 (Box 13)
  - Northern Telecom, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Northwest Airlines, 1991-1992; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance, 1990-1994 (Box 13)
  - Nutritional Research Foundation, 1977 (Box 13)
  - On the Twentieth Century, 1978 (Box 13)
  - Orion Pictures--RoboCop 3, 1993 (Box 13)
  - Orkin, 1976 (Box 13)
  - Orkin--Press kit, 1977 (Box 13)
  - Oscar Mayer, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Pan Am--Press kit, 1977 (Box 13)
  - Paramount, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Payless Drug Stores, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Pepsi, 1981-1987; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Perdue, 1974-1984 (Box 13)
  - Phillips Petroleum (with Tom Seaver), 1972 (Box 13)
  - Presto Foods, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Prodigy, 1992-1995; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Publicker (Inver House), 1974 (Box 13)
  - Puppy Kibbles 'n Bits, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Radio City Music Hall, 1979-1980; 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Radio City Music Hall--Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Radio City Music Hall--Clippings, 1979 (Box 36)
  - Radio City Music Hall--Clippings, 1979-1980 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Radio City Music Hall--Kids Club/Burger King, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Radio City Music Hall--Manhattan Showboat, 1980 (Box 13)
  - Radio City Music Hall--New York Summer, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Radio City Music Hall--Snow White, 1979-1980; 6 folders (Box 13)
  - Radio City Music Hall--The 1940s Radio Hour, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Radio City Music Hall--The Great American Children's Hour, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Radio City Music Hall--Various (includes Snow White, New York Summer), 1979 (Box 35)
  - RCA, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
  - Readers Digest--Advertising Department, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Common Market, 1963-1964; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Danny Thomas, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Earn-Learn Tour, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Faculty Viewpoint, 1963 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Faculty Viewpoint: Is the Monroe Doctrine Dead?, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Faculty Viewpoint: Japan's Economy Goes Boom, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Faculty Viewpoint: Let's Look Again at Those IQ Tests, 1961 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Faculty Viewpoint: Our Foreign Service, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Faculty Viewpoint: Our Population Crisis Is Here and Now, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Faculty Viewpoint: Peace Corps, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Faculty Viewpoint: Plot to Abolish Childhood, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Faculty Viewpoint: The Case for Chastity, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Faculty Viewpoint: The Five-Hour Day, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Faculty Viewpoint: The Hidden Danger in Subsidized Marriage, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Forum on Transportation, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Guns by Mail, 1965; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Guns by Mail--Clippings, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Guns by Mail--Dan Seymour correspondence, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Guns by Mail--Kiwanis Club, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Guns by Mail--Police Chief survey, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Guns by Mail--Senator Thomas Dodd, 1965; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--"Have you ever been convicted of a felony?" forum, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Hidden Threat to Children's Eyes, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Hidden Threat to Children's Eyes--Amblyopia, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Hidden Threat to Children's Eyes--Delta Gamma, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Hidden Threat to Children's Eyes--Preschool vision screening, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Let's Beautify America, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Let's Beautify America--Awards, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Let's Beautify America--Biographies, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Let's Beautify America--Clippings, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Let's Beautify America--Follow-up correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Let's Beautify America--General correspondence, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Let's Beautify America--Historic Chart of Alexandria, Virginia, 1963 (Box 36)
  - Readers Digest--Let's Beautify America--Letters from Mayors, 1965; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Let's Beautify America--National Clean Up-Paint Up-Fix Up Bureau pamphlets, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Let's Beautify America--Photographs, 1965; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Let's Beautify America--Proclamations, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Let's Beautify America--Thank you letters, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Let's Beautify America--Tour material, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Look at the New Flying Machines, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Macalester College, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Macalester College--Program for international journalists, 1961 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Physical Fitness, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Protest against Storm King Mountain Dam (New York), 1964 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Public relations plan, 1963 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Readers Digest Foundation, 1963-1964 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--RCA Victor Record Club, 1961-1964 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Teens and Alcohol, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--This Nation Under God, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Yogi Berra, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Readers Digest--Young Lives, Brave Actions (Young Americans Medal for Bravery), 1965; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Readers Digest--Young Lives, Brave Actions (Young Americans Medal for Bravery)--Wisconsin, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Readers Digest--Your Eyes, Your Auto and Your Life, 1965; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Reynolds Aluminum, 1986-1987 (Box 15)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1991-1996 (Box 15)
  - Rheingold, 1974 (Box 15)
  - R.J. Reynolds (Winston)--France, 1987 (Box 15)
  - Rolex, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Rowntree Mackintosh, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Royal Canadian Mint, 1985 (Box 15)
  - R.T. French, 1982 (Box 15)
  - R.T. French--Recipe hunt, 1974 (Box 15)
  - Rustenburg Platinum Mines, 1976-1977 (Box 15)
  - Ryder Truck, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Salada, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Salvation Army, 1964-1977; 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Samsonite, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Samsonite--Goolagong, Palmer, 1976 (Box 15)
  - Samsonite--Pittsburgh Steelers, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Saratoga Water, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Save Grand Central Station, 1977 (Box 15)
  - S.C. Johnson, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Schick, 1985-1987 (Box 15)
  - Schlitz, 1981-1982; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Scientific American, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Booklets, 1960-1966 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Junior Miss, 1965-1966 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Junior Miss interview suggestions, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Junior Miss--Off to a Beautiful Start, 1964 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Junior Miss--Party Planning, 1965; 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Lady Scott, 1967 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Lady Scott personality campaign, 1968 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Publicity-Education program, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Scotties, 1986 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Ultra, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Viva, 1967-1969 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Viva--Anti-Bounty, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Viva--Cartier, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Viva--From Rags to Riches, 1968 (Box 15)
  - Scott Paper--Viva photographs, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Screenvision, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Seven-Up, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Seven-Up Uncola, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Showtime/The Movie Channel, 1984-1986 (Box 15)
  - Signal, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Simmons Mattress, 1974 (Box 15)
  - Singer Sewing Machine, 1963-1972; 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Sinutab, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Six Flags, 1977-1987 (Box 15)
  - Sperry New Holland, 1973-1976 (Box 15)
  - Spiegel, 1974 (Box 15)
  - Spy Magazine, 1992 (Box 15)
  - St. Lucia Tourist Board, 1980 (Box 15)
  - Standard Brands, 1960-1969; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands, 1966 (Box 36)
  - Standard Brands--4-H awards program, 1969 (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands--4-H Bread Awards, 1964-1969; 4 folders (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands--4-H Club Congress, 1965-1969; 12 folders (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands--4-H Club Congress/County Agents dinner, 1965 (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands--4-H Club Madison Wisconsin, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands--4-H Clubs, 1965-1966 (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands--4-H Clubs--Inner city outreach, 1965 (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands--4-H County Extension Agents Meeting, 1967 (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands--4-H Donors Conference, 1969 (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands--4-H Negro Bread Winners, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands--4-H State Winners favorite recipes, 1969 (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands--Activities, 1960-1964 (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands--Alicia and Amparo (bilingual Spanish/English columns: Alicia Escribe, Consejos caseros por amparo), 1967-1968; 3 folders (Box 16)
  - Standard Brands--American Gas Association workshop, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--American Home Economics Association (AHEA), 1965-1967; 4 folders (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--American School Food Service Association, 1961-1966 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Best of All Days cooking school report, 1965 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Booklets and offers, 1965-1972; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Brazil, 1967 (Box 35)
  - Standard Brands--California Raisin Advisory Board, 1965-1966 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Catering to a Crowd, undated (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Chase and Sanborn history, 1964 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Coma Mas Pan (Spanish recipes), 1957 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Cool Rise method, 1966 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--County Extension Agents, 1969 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Depressed area mailing, 1961 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Dietary Fat Guide and Recipe Book, 1965-1966 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Elizabeth Scott "Letters from Elizabeth", 1968-1969 (Box 35)
  - Standard Brands--Extension home economics meeting, 1966 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Extension Homemaker promotion kit, 1965 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Fair program, 1959; 4 folders (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Farm Editors Conference, 1963-1965 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Favorite Bread Recipes from National 4-H Winners, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Favorite Canadian Recipes, 1963 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Fleischmann--Binder, 1959-1963; 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Fleischmann--Margarine Calorie Subtractor, 1968 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Fleischmann--Meal planning contest, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Fleischmann--Meal planning contest winners' European trip, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Fleischmann--Menu planning contest, 1965-1967; 5 folders (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Fleischmann--Treasury of Yeast Baking, 1962-1966; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Standard Brands--Formulas Fleischmann (Spanish recipes), undated (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Foundation for Business Education, 1959-1960 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Good letters, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Have Fun Make Rolls, 1962-1965 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Inside Information (home demonstration newsletter), 1963-1965 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Inter-American Rural Youth Leaders' conference, 1964 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--International, 1965-1969; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--International (includes "Letters from Elizabeth"), 1967-1968 (Box 35)
  - Standard Brands--International correspondence, 1967-1969; 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--International Food Fair, 1963; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--International photographs, 1968-1970 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--International recipes, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--International reports, 1966-1968; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--International--Yeast for Health, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--JWT Produces Award-Winning Food Booklets, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Live Better Electrically, 1965 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Low Sodium Diets Can Be Delicious (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Menu planning contest, 1964-1966; 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Menu planning contest--Atlantic City, 1965; 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Menu planning contest--Lists of winners, 1965 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Menu planning contest--Sister M. Dorothea, 1965 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Menu planning contest--Sisters photographs, 1965 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Mexico, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--National Association of Extension 4-H Agents, 1969; 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--National Association of Extension Home Economists, 1965; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Nutrition education (U.S. and South Africa), 1958-1960 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Our Daily Bread, undated (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Parties in Motion (getting men involved in party planning), 1966 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Peanut oil information, 1963-1964 (Box 18)
  - Standard Brands--Philippines, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Photograph binders, 1971-1976; 6 folders (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Planters, 1962 (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Planters--Home Service Director mailings, 1964 (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Planters--Marketing to Kosher/Passover, 1965-1966 (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Planters--Materials on nutrition and fitness aimed at children, 1967-1970 (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Planters--Mr. Peanut booklets, 1962-1967 and undated; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Planters--Mr. Peanut School Champ, 1966 (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Planters--Potato chips, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Posters, undated (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Standard Brands--Puerto Rico, 1966-1968; 4 folders (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Pyrofax baking contest, 1962-1964 (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Recipes, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Royal, 1964-1967; 4 folders (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Royal--Cakes, 1957 (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Royal--Recipe booklets, 1966 and undated (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Royal--Recipe searc h, 1965 (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Royal--Royal products binders, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands--Royal--Royal products binders, 1965-1970; 5 folders (Box 20)
  - Standard Brands--Royal--South Africa, 1968 (Box 35)
  - Standard Brands--South Africa, 1967 (Box 35)
  - Standard Brands--South Africa, 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Standard Brands--South Africa--Nutrition posters, 1968 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Standard Brands--South Africa--Party Time in Royal Rhyme, undated (Box 20)
  - Standard Brands--Surplus foods welfare questionnaire (with responses), 1965 (Box 20)
  - Standard Brands--U.S. government food stamp program, 1960-1962 (Box 20)
  - Standard Brands--Welfare mailing (New York), 1961 (Box 20)
  - Standard Brands--When You Bake With Yeast, 1961 and undated; 2 folders (Box 20)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes: Have Fun Make Rolls; Breads of Many Lands; Holiday Breads
  - Standard Brands--Why Do Women Bake with Yeast?, 1964 (Box 20)
  - Standard Brands--Yeast Breads Plain and Fancy, 1961 (Box 20)
  - Standard Brands--Yeast-Riz, 1965 (Box 20)
  - Standard Brands--Young Cook's Bake a Bread Book, 1965 (Box 20)
  - Standard Brands/Scott Paper--You're Entertaining (Junior Miss hostess guides), 1963-1965 (Box 20)
  - Standard Brands/Seven-Up--World's Fair, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
  - Standard Federal Savings, 1986 (Box 20)
  - Standard Milling Company recipe cards, undated (Box 20)
  - Statue of Liberty, 1985-1986 (Box 20)
  - Stick To Your Ribs restaurant, 1992 (Box 20)
  - STP (Drackett), 1976-1978; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - STP (Drackett)--Pro bowling sponsorship, 1975-1976 (Box 20)
  - STP (Drackett)--Robert Blake, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Sun Banks of Florida, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Survival Anglia, 1976-1978 (Box 20)
  - Taft Broadcasting, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Tassaway, 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Teledyne legal, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Tenneco, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Textron, 1974-1977 (Box 20)
  - The Crucifer of Blood, 1978 (Box 20)
  - Timex, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Toys R Us, 1982-1995; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Uncle Ben's, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Uncle Ben's (Australia)--J.S. Ibbotson, "As Others See Us", 1975 (Box 35)
  - Unilever, 1977-1994; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Unilever--Shield, 1981 (Box 20)
  - University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey--Copsa Institute for Alzheimer's Disease, 1995 (Box 20)
  - US Air, 1979-1986 (Box 20)
  - U.S. Brewers Association, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
  - U.S. Brewers Association--Parties in Motion, 1960s (Box 20)
  - U.S. Brewers Association--Shrimp and Beer Party mailing, 1965 (Box 20)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1991 (Box 20)
  - Vanderbilt Medical Center, 1986 (Box 20)
  - Vanderbilt YMCA, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Volkswagen, 1963-1985 (Box 20)
  - Vons Grocery, 1987 (Box 20)
  - W.A. Taylor, 1976 (Box 20)
  - W.A. Taylor--Courvoisier, 1986 (Box 20)
  - W.A. Taylor--VSOP (with Herbie Hancock's VSOP band), 1977 (Box 20)
  - Walker Manufacturing, 1980 (Box 20)
  - Wall Street Journal, 1992-1996 (Box 20)
  - Warner Bros., 1975 (Box 20)
  - Warner-Lambert, 1991-1994 (Box 20)
  - Warner-Lambert--Chiclets, 1993-1996 (Box 20)
  - Warner-Lambert--Clorets, 1993-1994 (Box 21)
  - Warner-Lambert--EPT (pregnancy test kit), 1992-1995; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Warner-Lambert--Hall's, 1994-1996 (Box 21)
  - Warner-Lambert--Listerine, 1974, 1992-1994; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Warner-Lambert--Rolaids, 1996 (Box 21)
  - Warner-Lambert--Schick, 1987-1996; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Warner-Lambert--Schick Silk Effects (with Angie Everhart), 1996 (Box 21)
  - Warner-Lambert--Trident, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Warner-Lambert--Zantac, 1996-1997 (Box 21)
  - Weather Channel, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Wedgwood, 1973-1986 (Box 21)
  - Weight Watchers, 1995-1996 (Box 21)
  - Western Center on Law and Poverty, 1979 (Box 21)
  - White Castle, 1993 (Box 21)
  - Wm. Underwood, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Women's Tennis Association (WTA), 1993 (Box 21)
  - WXIA-TV, 1975 (Box 21)
- Events and Activities, 1972-1995 and undated; 3
  - A Gorey Halloween, 1978 (Box 21)
  - AAF Hall of Fame luncheon, 1979 (Box 21)
  - Advertising Age--International Creative Seminar, 1975-1976 (Box 21)
  - American Jewish Committee Awards, 1974 (Box 21)
  - Andy Awards, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Art Directors Party (Caroline Diehl), 1979 (Box 21)
  - Automotive Aftermarket Seminar, 1975; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Awards programs, 1977 (Box 21)
  - Belmont outing, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Black Achievers Awards, 1977 (Box 21)
  - Blood Bank drive, 1974 (Box 21)
  - Blood drive, 1977 (Box 21)
  - Business-Professional Advertising Association--Mary Wells Lawrence speech, 1977 (Box 21)
  - Caples Awards, 1987 (Box 21)
  - CEBA Black Network Awards, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Cerebral Palsy Bike-a-thon, 1977-1979 (Box 21)
  - Channel 13 auction, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Chinese delegation visit, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Clio Awards, 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Commercial Zapping Symposium, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Consumer in Crisis Seminar, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Cresmer Woodward O'Mara and Ormsbee Sales Seminar, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Effie Awards, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Ethics in Advertising, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Food Marketing Symposium (with Secretary of Agriculture John Block), 1985 (Box 21)
  - Fortune Corporate Communications Seminar, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Fragasso Awards, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Glamour (magazine) Seminar, 1977 (Box 21)
  - Globo TV Seminar, 1995 (Box 21)
  - Harlem Youth Speaks, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Helen Federico art exhibit at JWT New York, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Imperial Defense College (UK) meeting, 1973 (Box 21)
  - International Advertising Seminar, 1974 (Box 21)
  - IRTF intern visit, 1975 (Box 21)
  - J. Walter People program, 1985 (Box 21)
  - J. Walter Wardrobe, undated (Box 21)
  - Joe O'Donnell subway party, 1986 (Box 21)
  - JWT 130th anniversary, 1994 (Box 21)
  - JWT 130th anniversary, 1994 (Box 22)
  - JWT 130th anniversary--Ecuador, 1994 (Box 22)
  - JWT 130th anniversary--Expenses, 1994 (Box 22)
  - JWT 130th anniversary--Invitation lists, 1994 (Box 22)
  - JWT 130th anniversary--J. Walter Gene, 1994 (Box 22)
  - JWT 130th anniversary--Lima, Peru, 1994 (Box 22)
  - JWT 130th anniversary--Photographs, 1994 (Box 22)
  - JWT 130th anniversary--Review, 1994 (Box 22)
  - JWT Annual Meeting, 1973-1982; 4 folders (Box 22)
  - JWT Annual Stockholder Meeting materials, 1976 (Box 22)
  - JWT Board dinner, 1986 (Box 22)
  - JWT Board of Directors Meeting, 1974-1976; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - JWT Communications Committee meeting, 1972-1977 (Box 22)
  - JWT Craft Show, 1974-1975 (Box 22)
  - JWT Day at the Races, 1984 (Box 22)
  - JWT European Managers Meeting, 1995 (Box 22)
  - JWT European PR Council Meeting, 1995 (Box 22)
  - JWT European PR Directors Meeting, 1993 (Box 22)
  - JWT Family Hoedown (Phililppines), 1975 (Box 22)
  - JWT Lake Lawn Seminar, 1975 (Box 22)
  - JWT Latin American Managers Meeting, undated (Box 22)
  - JWT New York Office Sail-a-thon, 1976 (Box 22)
  - JWT North American Managers Meeting, 1995 (Box 22)
  - JWT office openings, 1972-1975 (Box 22)
  - JWT Operations Committee Meeting, 1982 (Box 22)
  - JWT PR Directors Meeting, 1992-1994; 3 folders (Box 22)
  - JWT Research Conference, 1977 (Box 22)
  - JWT Stockholders Meeting, 1974-1975; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - JWT Talent Show, 1992-1994 (Box 22)
  - JWT training programs, 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - JWT Worldwide PR Council Meeting, 1995; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - JWT/Client Research Conference, 1975 (Box 22)
  - Key events schedule, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Lease/Move to 466 Lexington, 1979-1982; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Lease/Move to 466 Lexington, undated; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Lease/Move to 466 Lexington--Press coverage, 1979 (Box 23)
  - Lease/Move to 466 Lexington--Press kits, 1979 (Box 23)
  - Mayor's Volunteer Service Awards, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Media Managers Meeting, 1975 (Box 23)
  - Media Relations Month, 1975 (Box 23)
  - Mr. T party, 1985 (Box 23)
  - National creative awards competition, 1987 (Box 23)
  - National Merit Scholarships (JWT participation/sponsorship), 1976-1982 (Box 23)
  - NATPE (National Association of Television Program Executives) Conference, 1977-1979; 3 folders (Box 23)
  - NOW (National Organization for Women) "badvertising" seminar, 1974 (Box 23)
  - Photographs, 1987 (Box 23)
  - Publicity meetings, presentations, 1975 (Box 23)
  - RSVP Tribute to Corporate Volunteers, 1995 (Box 23)
  - Security Analysts Meeting, 1975-1978 (Box 23)
  - Social events, 1985 and undated; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Society of Illustrators exhibit, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Student fellowship summer intern program, 1975 (Box 23)
  - Summer party, Club Getaway, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Super Bowl study mailing, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Super Bowl XIX, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Survival Anglia meeting, 1987 (Box 23)
  - Thompson Night--Caspar Weinberger, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Thompson Night--Daniel Patrick Moynihan, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Thompson Night--Henry Kissinger, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Thompson Night--Jack Kemp, 1994 (Box 23)